https://immaculateflight.com/terms/

Immaculate Flight
Term & Conditions | Immaculate Flight
Multiple cabin cleaning and disinfection options available, please email sales@immaculateflight.com for all inquiries!
Toggle navigation
MenuAircraft Cleaning ServicesInterior Aircraft CleaningInterior Aircraft CleaningGeneral Cleaning & DetailingCarpet cleaningLeather Cleaning & ReconditionLavatory Cleaning CloseExterior Aircraft CleaningExterior Aircraft CleaningAircraft WashingBrightwork – Metal PolishingPaint Protection – Sealing & WaxingDe-Ice Boot Strip & ResealGear Well Cleaning CloseMobile Aircraft ServicesMobile Aircraft ServicesMobile Aircraft General Cleaning & Detailing CloseCustomized ServicesCustomized ServicesCustomized Services General Cleaning & Detailing CloseGet a free quote CloseLocationsSolutionsPrivate OperatorsFlight DepartmentsFBOsMROsCommercial AirlinesSpecial Events CloseAboutLeadershipCommitment to SafetyIndustry MembershipsCareers CloseContactNew ClientsExisting ClientsFeedback Close888.858.5123
Close
Aircraft Cleaning Services
Interior Aircraft Cleaning
Exterior Aircraft Cleaning
Mobile Aircraft Services
Customized Services
Locations
Solutions
Terms
By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Immaculate Flight’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Immaculate Flight’s web site;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Immaculate Flight at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
Disclaimer
The materials on Immaculate Flight’s web site are provided “as is”. Immaculate Flight makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Immaculate Flight does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
Limitations
In no event shall Immaculate Flight or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Immaculate Flight’s Internet site, even if Immaculate Flight or a Immaculate Flight authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Immaculate Flight’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Immaculate Flight does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Immaculate Flight may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Immaculate Flight does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
Links
Immaculate Flight has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Immaculate Flight of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.
Site Terms of Use Modifications
Immaculate Flight may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
Governing Law
Any claim relating to Immaculate Flight’s web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Michigan without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of your personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy:
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Display Advertising
ImmaculateFlight.com has implemented Display Advertising and uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. This means that third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on websites across the Internet.
ImmaculateFlight.com along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.
If you want to opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, just customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings or using Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on that will instruct the Google Analytics JavaScript not to send any information about the website visit to Google Analytics.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
ImmaculateFlight.com may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of ImmaculateFlight.com websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
Questions or Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at marketing@immaculateflight.com.
